Hello friends, welcome to
Engineers W where we talk about
stock market insights,
quarterly results of companies and news related to stock splits and
bonuses.  So
friends, today we will talk
about the quarter one results of ICICI LBD.
They have published their quarter one results.
So let's see
friends how their quarter one
result has been.  First of all, let me tell you that all the
figures shown here are in lakhs.
So whatever I tell you, I will
tell you after converting it into crores.  So his
total income has been ₹83 crores.  Which
was ₹5851 crore in the last quarter, which
was ₹5351 crore in the same quarter last year.  So here we
see a jump of around 15%.  If we
talk about their expenses, their expenses have been Rs 5429
crores which was Rs 5435 crores in the last quarter.
So their expenses have
not increased much on a quarter-on-quarter basis.
But on year on year basis, there is a jump in it
which has increased from Rs 4850 crore to Rs
5429 crore.  Now if we talk about their PAT, the
net profit is
reported to be Rs 747 crore, which
was Rs 59 crore in the last quarter and Rs
580 crore in the same quarter last year.  So here
we are seeing a good growth which is
around 27-28%.
Friends, the company has also declared dividend.  So the
dividend declared is a dividend of ₹7
which was ₹6 in the same quarter last year.
So the company has also increased this dividend.
If we talk about their EPS growth in terms of
earnings per share, then the
EPS they have reported is ₹15
which was ₹10 in the last quarter.   It was
around ₹11 and last year
in the same quarter it was around ₹12.  So here also
we see growth of around 28-29%.
Now if we look at their overall results, the
top line has also grown by about 15% and the
bottom line has also grown by 28 to 29%.
So this is a steady result.
They have given good results.  Let's see
what impact these results have on their shares.
So here are their quarter one
results.  Friends, before making any investment, do
not forget to take advice from your stock market advisor who is SEBI registered.  This
video is for educational purposes only.  There
may be risks involved.  Therefore,
definitely take advice from your advisor.
Friends, if you liked the video then do
not forget to comment.  Please like, share and
subscribe so that we
get the motivation to make more videos.
See you guys in the next video
with the results of some other company.  Until then,
happy investing.